So, let's define the Precision metric as follows.
精度指标的定义如下
下面是医疗模型的混淆矩阵
Here is the Confusion matrix of the medical model.
我们用红色叉号表示要务必避免的情形
And we've added a red X in the spot that we really want to avoid,
which is the false negatives.
即假阴性
精度可以帮助回答
So Precision will be the answer to a question out of
all the points predicted to be positive,
在所有预测为阳性的点中
有多少是真阳性的点？
how many of them were actually positive?
In this case, the question translates to,
在这种情况下 该问题就相当于
在诊断为生病的所有患者当中
out of all the patients that we diagnosed as sick,
有多少位真正的生病了？
how many were actually sick?
精度是这列
So Precision is this column,
因为这列是诊断为生病的患者
because this column are the sick patients that we diagnosed as sick.
也就是 1000（诊断正确的人数）除以 1800
So it is 1000 that were correct divided by 1800,
which is the total number of patients diagnosed as sick.
即所有诊断为生病的患者人数
结果是 55.6%
This number is 55.7%.
数字不太大 因为不是很精确的模型
It's not a high number because this is not a very precise model.
但可以接受 因为我们要避免这个红色 X
But again, this is okay because what we're doing is avoiding this red X.
现在看看垃圾邮件模型 精度是多少？
Now, let's look at the spam e-mail model. What is this Precision?
在这个模型中 精度很重要
Now, know that in this model Precision is very important,
因为要避免的红色 X 位于这列
because the red X that we're avoiding is in this column.
红色 X 是不小心发送到垃圾文件夹的非垃圾邮件
The red X is the non-spam emails that were accidentally sent to the spam folder.
So those 30 errors are really bad and we want to avoid them.
这 30 个错误很糟糕 我们需要避免它们
So again, Precision says,
精度表示
out of all the e-mails sent to the spam folder,
在所有发送到垃圾文件夹的电子邮件当中
有多少实际上是垃圾邮件？
how many of them were actually spam?
也就是 100（正确分类的垃圾邮件）
So we have 100, which are correct,
divide it by 130,
除以 130
即发送到垃圾文件夹的所有邮件
which is all the ones we've sent to the spam folder.
结果是 76.9% 更高了
This number is 76.9% which is higher.
This is better, since this model needs high Precision,
这样更好 因为这个模型需要高精度
因此这个数字最好很大
so the number better be big.
Now, let's do an exercise.
现在做道练习
Let's go to our linear model over here.
转到这里的线性模型
What is the Precision of this linear model?
该线性模型的精度是多少？
Enter your answer below.
请将答案填在下方